Khairul Umam

SUMMARY

Accomplished Glints Academy as a Backend Developer and has more than 1-year of working experience in the airports' industry. Skilled in Javascript (Node-Js, express-Js, React-Js), PHP (Codeinigter, Laravel), Java, SASS, SQL and passionate in providing tech products that the society needs. Seek an opportunity to help a company to develop their product as a Backend, Frontend, or Fullstack Developer, as well as grow and develop my own skills as a coder.



https://github.com/riorocker75



Medan Kota, Sumatera Utara 20114



umamcore94<u>@gmail.com</u>



+62 85275441200

EDUCATION

Back End Developer Glints Academy Batch 15 Sept 2021 - Jan 2022

Informatics Engineer Universitas Malikussaleh Sept 2012 – July 2017

LANGUAGE

English-Intermediate
Bahasa Indonesia-Native Speaker

EXPERTISE

Javascript (Node-js, Express-Js, React-Js) PHP (Codeinigter, Laravel) Go Java(Spring) CSS (SASS, SCSS) SQL NoSQL (Mongoose)

EXPERIENCE

Id/x Partner - FullStack Engineer

(April 2022 - now)

- Responsible for Enhancement app as frontend
- Learned and Implementing React to Java Spring
- Coordinated and work together with backend, and Talend team for deploying app.

HAAC GLOBAL - Backend Developer

(Jan 2022 - Jun 2022)

- Responsible for Web and Mobile APi's.
- Design Api's flow
- Learned and Implementing Payment APi's
- Coordinated and work together with other frontend web and mobile team of Haac Global.

Glints Academy Bootcamp - Backend Developer (Sept 2021 - Jan 2022)

- Learned basic computer science and Back End fundamentals like Javascript, NodeJs, ExpressJs, ORM, and ODM, also learned unit testing and CI/CD using AWS EC2
- Learned and Implementing Agile Methodology (SCRUM) with Trello on Glints Mini Project and Final Project
- Coordinated and work together with other Back End team members on Glints Final Project

Freelance as Fullstack Developper

(Jan 2017 - Jan 2020)

 Responsible for creating simple or complicated system information based on Laravel framework and Codeinigter.

Apprenticeship as Junior Backend Developer at Angkasa Pura Solution

(Jan 2016 - Oct 2016)

- Responsible for creating FIDS (Flight Information Display) application which is a platform to display flight information to passengers.
- Design an application to call passenger during their departure schedule.Design a RestAPI

using PHP native to provide requests and response from the database to user.

Lecture Assistance for Web Development

(March 2015 - May 2015)

 Coordinated and teach 30+ students to assure completed the class

Apprenticeship at Angkasa Pura II

(May 2015 - July 2015)

• Joining as their junior network engineer

PORTFOLIO

Glints Academy Final Project: Talikasih

Talikasih is an platform to share and open donation Link: https://bit.ly/317J2d6

Freelance Project: Koperasi Simpan Pinjam

https://github.com/riorocker75/koperasi baru.git